

## **Enrique Marín Hirales Frontend Web Developer** La Paz, BCS, México

enriquemarin.xyz

#### **Contact**

**.** +52 (612) 104 9341

➡ enrique.marin.h@hotmail.com

in /enriquemarin

#### About me

I am a young developer enthusiastic about innovative and technological projects that seek to impact people's lives.

In recent years I have worked in areas such as web development and mobile Apps, as well as graphic creation projects such as branding and digital marketing.

## Skills

## </> Front End Development

Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Javascript, Typescript, Post CSS with SASS, Bootstrap, MUI with Vuetify, React.

#### </> Back End Development

Node.js with Express, Adonis.js, Strapi, MySQL, MongoDB.

#### Tools & Services

VS Code, Github, Heroku, DigitalOcean, AWS, Cloudinary, Figma, Illustrator.

## Languages

Spanish English intermediate (B2) Native

## Some projects



#### Tresam Capital

Professional Website made it when I worked on Applab.mx

tresamcapital.com



#### Capbook

Dashboard created to set a base grid template for my projects

capbook.vercel.app



## Landfinder México

Real estate website to find projects to invest

landfindermexico.com



#### Hates (hotdogs) Map

Web App to find and register street hotdogs. Open project

hates-map.vercel.app

To see more, check out my Github



# **Experience**



**Applab.mx** Sep 2021 - Jan 2022 (4 months)

## Front End Web Developer (Remote)

I worked on websites for businesses and clients looking for a more customized design. I also worked on a project in production for a German company called Bits&Birds in which we developed a large platform for the management of vacancies and candidates, working continuously hand in hand with the development team of that company.



**Freelance** 2020 - 2021

#### Brand designer, UI designer & Web Development

Independent professional focused on development services of web systems, brand design, interface design (UI / UX).



**Async Agencia Creativa** 2019 - 2022

## CoFounder, Designer & Web Developer

Async is an agency dedicated to inpulse companies and entrepreneurs into the digital world through branding, marketing and websites.



Relapp 2019 (6 months)

## Brand Designer, UI Designer & App Developer (Flutter)

App sudcalifornian to search all kind of local business and promos in your town. We developed this app with Flutter using Firebase for backend, and we deployed on Google Play Store and App Store.



JastMedia 2018 (2 months)

## Front End Developer, Content Loader

Juniper Data Center's Extending Department Focused on Websites Development for clients in United States.

## **Education**



Bachelor in Computing Systems 2013-2018 Tecnológico Nacional de México Campus La Paz

Security and Web Development speciality

Certifications

You can see the certifications in my LinkedIn profile







